wpdiscounts.com 2019-07-12

# privacy policy - WPdiscounts

## Our **Privacy Policy**

At WPdiscounts.com the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.wpdiscounts.com and how it is used.

### Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from visitors in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when visitors visit our website, register on the website, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our website. Visitors may visit our website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from visitors only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.

### Information That is Gathered from Visitors

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor’s IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit. This information is not used to track individual visitors to this website. 

### Cookies

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website. Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. Also they may be used to track your return visits to the website. Where registration is required, the visitor’s email and a username will be stored on the server.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from access to certain features of the website (e.g. for cashback applications cookies are mandatory).

### Cookies and our use of Google Analytics

If a page of our website contains a link to the Google Analytics tracking code we are using Google, as a third party vendor of visitor logging. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. We do not share personal data with Google.

### Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent visitors personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding users and visitors with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the website or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

E-mail may be sent to inform you of news of our services or offers. You will always be given the chance to opt out of any periodic mailings. If you have subscribed to one of our email services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in e-mail that you receive.

### How we Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our website. Our website operates on a secure Linux server which is updated on a daily basis with any operating system updates or security patches that need applying.

### Third Party Content

Visitors may find advertising or other content on our website that links to the websites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these websites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website. In addition, these websites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These websites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Third-party ad Servers or ad Networks

Third-party ad servers or ad networks like Google Adsense use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on WPDiscounts.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. WPDiscounts has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. WPDiscounts’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
